It isn't hard ♪
To see, oh ♪
The hang-ups we have ♪
Today ♪
Said we need to strive for ♪
More liberty ♪
♪ Lift yourself up
on your feet ♪
Let's get it on ♪
♪ We've been fooling around,
my friends ♪
For much too long... ♪
Too long ♪
Too... ♪
- Huh?
- You ready to go?
Oh, no, y'all go ahead.
I'll catch up with you.
I got a "dep date."
Dep date?
A picnic with a deputy?
An underground Johnny Depp film
edited from all his old films.
You're both wrong.
Sensory deprivation tank,
one hour.
- You were closer.
- I was closer. Yeah.
Well, it's nice, man.
You know, it's just you alone
with your thoughts
floating in water.
It's like being
in the womb again,
replenishes your mind and soul.
You should try it.
Mm.
Yeah, um, I'll do that when
I, uh, have the time.
Yeah, I'll try it.
That almost always
certainly means no.
You need us to drop you off?
Nah, I got errands to run
on the way.
Don't come to this thing
with a full stomach.
Van'll be pissed.
I'm like a teenager.
I'll be hungry in an hour.
Old McAlfred ♪
Had a farm, E-I-E-I-O ♪
And on this farm ♪
♪ He broke his foot,
E-I-E-I-O ♪
With a fuck, fuck you ♪
- And a fuck, fuck you ♪
- Uh-huh.
Here a fuck, there a fuck ♪
Nigga, I'm-a fuck you up ♪
Old McAlfred had a farm ♪
- E-I... ♪
- Where he fucked your ho. ♪
Let's go.
You could've ended
stronger than that.
Straight from the Dec ♪
Came up, came down ♪
Stayed down, riding long ♪
♪ Stayed real,
caught the clown ♪
Took his crown, ATL. ♪
So, you park your own car,
you give 'em your keys,
- and they call it valet.
- Mm-hmm.
That's not valet to me. That's
giving a stranger your car keys.
I hate that shit.
That part.
Yeah, I thought the whole point
of valet was the parking.
Know what I'm saying? I should
be able to toss you my keys
and be like, "Nah, nigga,
keep it. I got another one."
- I don't understand it.
- Yeah.
So, this place, it's supposed
to have a really good spot.
Ooh, wait, wait, wait. Shit,
oh, shit. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Damn.
- Come on, bro.
- Oh, man,
I know exactly where
I'm going after this.
- You smell that?
- Yeah.
It smell like the manager
mean as hell.
You know, this is exactly why
we're going to this thing, okay?
You need to be able
to support your own.
God, man.
This is the first Black-owned
sushi restaurant in Atlanta. So...
This guy DeMarcus studied under
real sushi masters in Japan.
It's legit.
Okay, so they serve fried rice?
No, man, sushi. Sushi.
All right.
Van's friend invested
in this place, so, you know,
you'd be helping him out
a lot by eating here.
This it?
Oh, hold up, man.
Didn't this, uh,
used to be a Blockbuster?
Hell yeah, this used to be
a Blockbuster, man.
- Next.
- Oh.
I've got a prescription
for "Eze."
It's spelled E-Z-E,
like "Easy."
I mean, not like Eazy-E,
but E-Z-E.
One moment.
Yeah.
I don't see anything
here for you.
Are you sure? I mean, you guys
just sent me a notification, so...
Can you check the back?
Sorry, I'm just running late
for my float sesh.
- Uh...
- So... Thank you.
Mm.
Uh... I-I'm sorry,
I overheard
what you were saying.
Were you talking about
a sensory deprivation session
or shitting?
Uh, sensory deprivation,
actually.
I just started doing that
about a year ago.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
I go with a group
of girlfriends.
- It's the best.
- It's-it's great, right?
It's a sort of...
soothing therapy, really.
- It really is.
- Yeah.
We used to be a book club.
Now, we call ourselves
the Flo-teps.
The what? The Flo-teps?
- It's silly.
- It's clever.
You know, I, uh...
I had to stop going
because I got too deep into it.
The visions in the tank
can be so intense.
I started to lose track
of what was real.
Yes. I... I-I sometimes
get into it too much.
When-when that happens, though,
I found a little trick
to help anchor myself.
What is that?
Closer.
A thick Judge Judy.
Wait, wait a minute.
- What in the hell
are you saying?
- Shh, shh, shh...
Thick Judge Judy.
- Yeah.
- Like, thick thighs and tits?
Yes, and booty,
really, you know,
doesn't matter which body part
you use,
but, uh, the idea is...
...Judge Judy is always
on TV, right?
So, if I see her
and she's thick,
I know I'm in the tank.
Interesting.
Can I ask you something,
and I don't want to be, like,
too personal or anything, but
your prescription,
are you here for anxiety?
Oh, actually, no.
I'm-I'm here because my...
my baby needs antibiotics,
but I have done everything.
Zoloft, Lexapro, you name it.
N-Now I've changed,
completely changed my lifestyle.
I'm pretty much a vegan.
My baby's father
thinks I'm crazy,
but it-it works for me.
Yeah.
I think...
I think I was trained
for a long time
to look at this world
like a battle,
and, in some ways, it is.
But...
I'm a part of this world, too,
this big thing,
and I'm allowed to dance
in it how I want to.
As a matter of fact,
I demand that I do.
Mr. Eze.
Um...
Thank you.
Hey.
Can I say something?
Of course.
You have a beautiful spirit.
Thank you for sharing
your time with me.
Wow.
Thank you. You, uh...
I'm grateful for you, too.
Maybe I'll catch you
in a dep sesh sometime.
Or I'll catch you.
Be well.
- Hey.
- Sup, boo?
- Sorry.
- It's okay.
- Enjoy.
- Yeah, thank you, thank you.
- Thank you.
Thanks for coming, Al.
Yeah, no problem, not a problem.
Uh, they're really excited
that you're here,
so I think we'll get
good service.
Thank you.
The chef would like to meet with
you all before we get started,
if that's all right?
- Yeah, that's cool.
- Yeah, thank you.
- Yeah.
- Cool.
- Yeah, thank you.
- All right, cool.
I mean, if I'm-a do low tier,
I'm-a do it the right way.
- Come on, man,
that's not fair.
- Hell it ain't.
Y'all talking about Popeyes?
We'll go after, I promise.
I... I thought you wanted
to come here?
I do want to come here, but...
I can't stop thinking
about the Popeyes.
Why do you think I sat
facing away from it?
- Hello.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- What's going on?
- My name is Chef Kenny.
We'll be serving you
omakase today
since it's a special occasion.
DeMarcus is a big admirer
of your work,
and he's honored
to have you here.
Thank you.
Sup!
What's up!
♪ That mean I ain't
got to worry 'bout no ♪
Fuck nigga cheating... ♪
Darius!
Darius X.
Why you hiding from me, baby?
London? Oh!
Wait a... London.
I-I'm hiding from you?
You hiding from me.
I hit you up, like,
two months ago
about that, uh, that
lockdown party, you remember?
You know I change my number
every couple months.
- Facts.
- Email me, like
the underground days.
Uh... no.
Kind of put them days behind me.
What? Wait, wait, wait.
Come here.
- You used to be wild.
- No, you
used to be wild.
I was always safe.
Oh...
Mm...
Well...
it was nice to see you.
It was nice seeing you.
Hey. Where you headed?
Uh, sensory deprivation tank.
I got an appointment over there.
Where?
Bitch! Shut up!
What you say?
It's, uh, uptown.
I'm going that way anyway.
Get in. I want to catch up.
I mean, I could just walk.
I was already,
- uh...
- Boy, if you don't get in here.
F-R-E-E, fuck nigga free ♪
♪ That mean I ain't
got to worry... ♪
- Come on.
- All right.
- I want to catch up.
- Never question the queen.
Woo-hoo!
I love this song.
This shit got so much soul.
Shit is good.
- Weed?
- Oh, I...
I usually don't smoke
before these things, so...
But...
how often am I with London
from the south side?
There you go.
Can I have some
of that water?
Yeah, if you want
to get fucked up.
Huh?
That's vodka. You know
I'm lit.
I've been "macro-dosing"
all day.
Macro-dosing?
I haven't heard that one.
Shit!
Hand me my glasses.
- Damn.
- Put your foot
on that beer bottle.
I'm-a speed this thing up
a little bit,
air this thing out.
You are sober,
London.
Hello, Mr. Officer.
What seems to be the problem?
Appears you have
an illegal tint.
Really?
I'm sorry, this my mama car.
Your mother drives
a murdered-out Nissan Altima?
I know. My mom,
she got to stunt on them.
Have you been drinking
today, ma'am?
Of course not.
What's that right there?
- Water.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Yeah, if it were vodka,
would I do this?
Whoa...
Whoo!
Step out of the vehicle, ma'am.
Act white, just...
Step over to the curb
for me, please.
Walk a straight line.
Arms out wide.
Touch the tip of your nose
with your forefinger.
How many seasons of Homeboys
in Outer Space were there?
One.
You have a nice day, ma'am.
- What?
- Thank you.
10-4. All clear.
Hey!
Whoa! Whoa, whoa, whoa! Wait!
What're you doing with... Hey!
Are you crazy?
What are... what're you doing?
I don't know. Let's go.
How'd you even do that?
Like...
Whoa!
What?
- I'm sorry!
- What-what--
Where are you going?
I'm sorry!
This is all your fault!
What do you mean? Oh!
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine. I...
I guess I just kind of...
freaked out a little bit.
It's all right.
No, it's-it's all good.
It happens.
Would you like to take a break
in the tearoom?
Yes, tearoom. Let's do that.
Whew...
I'll fetch you some tea
in the tearoom
while you go relax
in the tearoom.
Oh, thanks.
You're welcome.
Is this your first time?
No, actually, I, uh,
come here once a week.
Cleanses my spirit.
Mm. I know.
My favorite part is the tearoom.
The tea in the tearoom
- is amazing for sure.
- Mm.
W-Why do y'all
keep saying "tearoom"?
Be-Because it's the tearoom.
Oh, my gosh. What is happening?
Wake up!
- I-I don't understand. I...
- Don't come back.
Hey. Hey, man,
I thought it was a dream.
Damn.
How's the chicken skin salad
going?
It's salty, man.
But not salty enough.
Excellent. Well, I'll be
right back with your next dish.
Let me take this
out of the way for you.
- Thank you.
- I'll take that, too.
- No problem.
Can we please
get the hell out of here?
What? No. We're not
doing that to them.
The rice has corn in it.
I just can't.
I fuck with
the yellow rice, okay?
Uh, points for the idea.
This shit is gross.
It's gross, man.
That chef over there
is making sushi rolls
with his bare-ass hands, Earn.
♪ Or one of us will leave here
tonight in a hearse ♪
♪ When we'll be tried by 12
and fertilizing daisies... ♪
Yeah, the fish is raw,
but it's warm.
Like, I feel like
that can't be safe.
Can we please...
can we just please
just go across the street, man,
get lunch real quick,
and stop lying
to these Black folk?
It's a Black sushi
fusion restaurant, okay?
There's gonna be a couple of
new ideas thrown at you, okay?
Can we please
keep our minds open?
Could I interest you on a refill
of, uh, hot white Hennessy?
♪ 'Cause I'd rather be
tried by 12... ♪
I need, I need, I need, uh,
I need the bathroom, man.
- Yeah, yeah, I gotcha.
- Uh, uh, got me on that?
All right. Cool. I'm-a just...
I'm-a run to the bathroom.
So we might catch a body... ♪
- Hey.
- Be careful.
- You got it, man?
- Hey, I'm good, man. I'm good.
All right.
Oh.
Hey, man.
Yo. What are you doing here?
Uh, I just was
in the neighborhood,
and, um, thought I'd come by.
You lying.
- Hey.
- Come on.
- What's up, man?
- What's up?
- Is it okay if I hug you?
- Of course, man.
- All right.
- Can't get no sicker.
All right.
- Come in, bro.
- Yo.
- Ugh.
- I was just, um...
Got something for you.
You know they deliver, right?
Yeah. I mean,
I got the app on my phone,
lets me know, so I just thought
I'd help you out.
- Ah. Well, that's nice.
- Yeah, well...
- Oh, come have this jollof.
- Yeah. Uh...
Wait. Wait. Who made jollof?
My roommate, bro.
Who the hell
you think made it?
Like, come on.
Um, I can't really
have any right now,
'cause I'm about to go meet up
with some people,
get some food, so...
Wait, you're not staying?
I'm kidding.
It's cool. Don't worry about it.
I mean, I'll stay
if you want me to.
Oh, boy, I don't want you
in here. I want you out there.
Have fun. Go see your people.
Great. Now I got the picture...
I'll take half a bowl of jollof.
Okay. I'm gonna get you
a full bowl.
- Just eat half.
- Okay. Thank you.
What else do you want?
I miss you, man.
Miss you.
How's Mom?
What about Dad?
Yeah.
...to get
a check cut and sent to us.
Pay your son's bills.
The case is dismissed.
They sound like very nice
people to me. Outrageous.
Whoa.
Damn.
Are you okay?
Hey, I thought you said I
couldn't turn over in here, man.
I-I've never seen that before.
Wait.
How long was I asleep?
I-I don't know.
About 30 minoots?
Maybe 35.
Wait. Wait. What?
30 minoo...!
You were gone for a while, man.
Yeah, man. That's 'cause, uh,
the bathroom was in the Rainbow
across the street.
Damn.
- I'm going to Popeyes right now.
- What?
Wait. We still have
the main meal.
Hey, do you know
what time it is?
You know what time it is?
It is 2:55 p.m.
That means, in five minutes,
that Popeyes across the street
is gonna be filled
with goddamn high schoolers.
And our only chance of getting
a goddamn chicken sandwich
is gonna be goddamn next week,
so I'm out, goddamn it.
- How was the bathroom, sir?
- Far, nigga. It was far.
Well, uh, we have a surprise
for you guys today.
It's the, uh, chef's special--
a very rare delicacy,
especially here in Georgia.
Blowfish cheek.
And as you all have
probably heard,
blowfish are extremely poisonous
and must be cut
with a skilled hand.
But Chef Kenny--
he studied with the finest,
and Demarcus oversaw
the cutting himself.
Itadakimasu.
Yeah, I ain't doing that, man.
- I'm sorry?
- I said I'm not doing it!
All right, look, thank y'all
for your service and everything.
The ambiance is beautiful,
the art is great,
but we... we got to go.
But, sir, the-the blowfish is
a rare delicacy. I can assure...
Yeah, man. I'm sure it is.
I'm sure it is, but we got...
I got a rap thing
that we got to go to, so, we...
- We double-booked.
- Yeah, sorry about that.
You're going to Popeyes.
Aren't you?
No, man. No.
Yes, you are.
They all do.
Look, I don't know what
you're talking about, man.
- We-we got to rap thing...
- You know,
there's a movie theater
two blocks away from here.
The night
Queen Slim premiered,
we were filled.
Line out the door.
Black people hopped up
on nationalism
coming to support their own.
15 minutes later,
we were empty.
Not one person ate the blowfish.
Not one.
Just a bunch of Yelp reviews
that all said the same thing.
"This nigga serving
poison fish."
- Hey, listen, man. I...
- Do you know
the traditional way to make
sushi is with your bare hands?
And that sushi should be served
at room temperature?
Every Japanese sushi restaurant
worth its soy sauce
does it that way,
and no one seemed to notice.
But if a brother
from Alabama
does it the same way,
suddenly, the fish is dirty.
- Yeah, but y'all serving us...
- You know, in Japan,
there's a sushi restaurant
that can't even
take reservations
from the general public
because it is so acclaimed?
You want to know where it is?
It's on the Ginza line
in a Tokyo subway station.
I know because my master,
Yuji Watanabe, studied there.
You see, he taught me
that it doesn't matter
where you serve the sushi.
A subway,
- an old Blockbuster Video.
- I knew it.
It doesn't matter.
He says, if the sushi's good,
people will come.
But I guess my master was never
a nigga from Florida.
- Listen, brother man.
- Don't give me
that "brother" shit!
This entire dinner,
you have been staring
across the street
at a modern-day Coon Chicken,
served to you by an Aunt Jemima,
who lies to you repeatedly,
telling you it is her recipe
and that she is benefiting
from it.
It is not her recipe.
You know who owns that recipe?
An Italian man and his family,
none of which
have married Black.
I heard some of them even moved
from New Orleans to New Jersey.
New... Jersey.
All right, man.
All right, I get it.
Oh, you get it?
Yeah. Yeah, I-I get it.
- You get it now?
- I get it now, man.
Then eat it.
- What?
- Eat it.
- Eat my poison fish, brother.
- Al...
Oh, let me guess.
You want some hot sauce
to go with it, brother?
All right, man. All right,
uh, you made your point,
- Demarcus, okay?
- Look outside.
That's the future.
That's our future.
Salted and battered.
Being sold back to us
in our own image.
See, the problem with us is
we don't trust each other.
"Don't trust a Chicago nigga,
they're shady."
"Don't believe niggas
from New Orleans,
they're slimy."
"Gotta watch out
for them New York niggas.
They're bound to hit a lick."
We've been told time
and time again
the only person you can trust...
...is yourself.
Right?
Lock the doors.
What?
Darius?
- Oh, shit!
- Ah!
Get in my pink Maserati.
It's outside. Go, go, go, go!
Hey, thanks again!
Fight me! Fight me!
Oh, shit.
That was the best Popeyes
- I've ever had in my life.
- It was good, right?
Oh, my God, yo.
Food tastes better when
you think you're about to die.
Oh, my God, man,
that shit is so true.
I was kind of scared, though.
You know that this, technically,
is all your fault.
I'm just playin'.
Hey, D, where the fuck
you get that car from, man?
I stole it.
This nigga.
- What you mean?
- What do you mean, man?
I stole it from the valet. Yeah.
- The...
- What?
Nigga, you had us
- in a stolen car?
- Are you serious?
You can get in trouble for that.
Nah, I'm not worried about
getting in trouble.
I'm still in the tank.
What?
Darius, you're not in the tank.
I am.
No, you're not in the tank.
You're really here,
and we're really your friends.
Maybe it's just, uh,
my dream,
and you are just in it.
Always have been.
Uh, well, okay.
Um... hey, y'all wanna smoke
some of my weed?
- Yeah.
- Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, let's do it, man.
No better time than now.
Don't worry, man,
it's gonna be fine.
Ah, well...
Just, I don't...
Hey, look. Hey, you rollin'.
- Whew.
- Do you know
how to roll one?
Ah, she knows.
I'll meet you out there, man.
- Hey, man.
- Huh?
- You wanna come?
- Oh, yeah, I'm coming.
I'm coming.
I will join you out there.
Just wait for me, sir.
- All right, well...
- Yeah.
- All right.
- Go.
All right, man.
- Oh, no.
- How long
is it gonna take?
I don't even know, man.
That's why I ain't even
part of that shit.
...is to make a decision
as to whether or not...
There's a song that I sing ♪
Whenever I'm sad ♪
Feeling bad ♪
There's a place in my head ♪
♪ That I go
when I'm feeling low ♪
I can trust in the melody ♪
In the song I can find me ♪
♪ Ever since I lost you,
I've been so lost, too ♪
In our love there is harmony ♪
♪ And I want to see
this love through with you ♪
There is a song you can sing ♪
There's a quiet place ♪
All you got to do is space ♪
There's a song ♪
That I sing ♪
Whenever I'm sad ♪
Feeling bad. ♪
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org